Jacques Seligmann & Co.
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Correspondence, 1913-1978, Series 1:; (80 linear feet)
  - Legal Correspondence Files, 1924-1978, 1.6:
    - The Story of Griselda Frescoes, 1923-1955, 1.6.5:
      This section of Subseries 1.6 includes correspondence and legal documents concerning the ownership and ensuing lawsuit over a series of Italian frescoes known as The Story of Griselda. The frescoes were originally acquired by the firm in the mid-1930s from Gabriel Dereppe and Ignatio (Ignace) G. Pollak in a very complicated legal agreement. Because the Italian government refused to let the frescoes leave the country, the firm entrusted their care to Mrs. Nanni Carla Politi and entered into a false sales transaction with her. Although Mrs. Politi did not actually buy the frescoes, documentation existed that made the transaction appear legitimate. Mrs. Politi then sold the frescoes to a Mr. Pelosi of Italy and kept the funds. These files document the complex trail and lawsuits surrounding the frescoes.
      - Correspondence and Agreements, 1932-1934 (Box 142, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence and Agreements, 1935-1937 (Box 142, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence and Agreements, 1946-1948 (Box 142, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence and Agreements, 1949 (Box 142, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence and Agreements, 1950-1952 (Box 142, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence and Agreements, 1953-1955 (Box 142, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence and Agreements, 1946-1949 (Box 142, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous Legal Files, 1927-1959, 1.6.6:
      - Agreement between Germain Seligman and Christopher Grey, Baron Glennconner, regarding Raeburn's Leslie Boy, 1927 (Box 142, Folder 10)
      - Customs Warehouse Fire, 1931 (Box 142, Folder 11)
      - Insurance Stock/Asset Valuations, 1955-1959 (Box 142, Folder 12)
      - Jacqueline Seligmann v. Germain Seligman and Jacques Seligmann & Co., Inc., 1954-1955 (Box 142, Folder 13)
  - Abstracts of Letters Sent, 1959-1967, 1.7:
    This subseries contains daily journals that provide two- or three-sentence abstracts of outgoing correspondence for 1959 through 1967. The firm's name for these documents was résumés; the staff of the Archives have renamed them abstracts for clarity.
    - Abstracts, 1958-1962 (Box 143, Folder 1)
    - Abstracts, 1963 (Box 143, Folder 2)
    - Abstracts, 1964 (Box 143, Folder 3)
    - Abstracts, 1964-1965 (Box 143, Folder 4)
    - Abstracts, 1966 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Abstracts, 1967 (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Letters Sent, 1965-1978, 1.8:
    This subseries includes carbon copies of outgoing correspondence for the years 1965 through 1978. As the firm was usually closed for month of August, most years do not have an August file. From 1975 through 1977 no files exist for July or August.
    Material within folders is generally arranged in reverse chronological order. This series has been scanned in entirety.
    - Letters Sent, 1965 January (Box 143, Folder 7)
    - Letters Sent, 1965 February (Box 143, Folder 8)
    - Letters Sent, 1965 March (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - Letters Sent, 1965 April (Box 143, Folder 10)
    - Letters Sent, 1965 May (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Letters Sent, 1965 June (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Letters Sent, 1965 July (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Letters Sent, 1965 September (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Letters Sent, 1965 October (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Letters Sent, 1965 November (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Letters Sent, 1965 December (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Letters Sent, 1966 January (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - Letters Sent, 1966 February (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - Letters Sent, 1966 March (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - Letters Sent, 1966 April (Box 144, Folder 11)
    - Letters Sent, 1966 May (Box 144, Folder 12)
    - Letters Sent, 1966 June (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Letters Sent, 1966 July (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Letters Sent, 1966 September (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Letters Sent, 1966 October (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Letters Sent, 1966 November (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Letters Sent, 1966 December (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Letters Sent, 1967 January (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Letters Sent, 1967 February (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Letters Sent, 1967 March (Box 145, Folder 9)
    - Letters Sent, 1967 April (Box 145, Folder 10)
    - Letters Sent, 1967 May (Box 145, Folder 11)
    - Letters Sent, 1967 June (Box 145, Folder 12)
    - Letters Sent, 1967 July (Box 145, Folder 13)
    - Letters Sent, 1967 August (Box 145, Folder 14)
    - Letters Sent, 1967 September-October (Box 146, Folder 1)
    - Letters Sent, 1967 October (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Letters Sent, 1967 November (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Letters Sent, 1967 December (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Letters Sent, 1968 January (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Letters Sent, 1968 February (Box 146, Folder 6)
    - Letters Sent, 1968 March (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Letters Sent, 1968 April (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - Letters Sent, 1968 May (Box 146, Folder 9)
    - Letters Sent, 1968 June (Box 146, Folder 10)
    - Letters Sent, 1968 July (Box 146, Folder 11)
    - Letters Sent, 1968 September (Box 146, Folder 12)
    - Letters Sent, 1968 October (Box 146, Folder 13)
    - Letters Sent, 1968 November (Box 146, Folder 14)
    - Letters Sent, 1968 December (Box 146, Folder 15)
    - Letters Sent, 1969 January (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Letters Sent, 1969 February (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Letters Sent, 1969 March (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Letters Sent, 1969 April (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Letters Sent, 1969 May (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Letters Sent, 1969 June (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Letters Sent, 1969 July (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Letters Sent, 1969 September (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Letters Sent, 1969 October (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Letters Sent, 1969 November (Box 147, Folder 10)
    - Letters Sent, 1969 December (Box 147, Folder 11)
    - Letters Sent, 1970 January (Box 147, Folder 12)
    - Letters Sent, 1970 February (Box 147, Folder 13)
    - Letters Sent, 1970 March (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Letters Sent, 1970 April (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Letters Sent, 1970 May (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Letters Sent, 1970 June (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Letters Sent, 1970 July (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Letters Sent, 1970 September (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Letters Sent, 1970 October (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Letters Sent, 1970 November (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - Letters Sent, 1970 December (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Letters Sent, 1971 January (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Letters Sent, 1971 February (Box 148, Folder 11)
    - Letters Sent, 1971 March (Box 148, Folder 12)
    - Letters Sent, 1971 April (Box 148, Folder 13)
    - Letters Sent, 1971 May (Box 148, Folder 14)
    - Letters Sent, June, 1971 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - Letters Sent, 1971 July (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Letters Sent, 1971 September (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Letters Sent, 1971 October (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Letters Sent, 1971 November (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Letters Sent, 1971 December (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Letters Sent, 1971 December-1972 January (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Letters Sent, 1972 February (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - Letters Sent, 1972 March (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - Letters Sent, 1972 April (Box 149, Folder 10)
    - Letters Sent, 1972 May (Box 149, Folder 11)
    - Letters Sent, 1972 June (Box 149, Folder 12)
    - Letters Sent, 1972 June-July (Box 149, Folder 13)
    - Letters Sent, 1972 September (Box 150, Folder 1)
    - Letters Sent, 1972 October (Box 150, Folder 2)
    - Letters Sent, 1972 November (Box 150, Folder 3)
    - Letters Sent, 1972 December (Box 150, Folder 4)
    - Letters Sent, 1973 January (Box 150, Folder 5)
    - Letters Sent, 1973 February (Box 150, Folder 6)
    - Letters Sent, 1973 March (Box 150, Folder 7)
    - Letters Sent, 1973 April (Box 150, Folder 8)
    - Letters Sent, 1973 May (Box 150, Folder 9)
    - Letters Sent, 1973 June (Box 150, Folder 10)
    - Letters Sent, 1973 July (Box 150, Folder 11)
    - Letters Sent, 1973 September (Box 150, Folder 12)
    - Letters Sent, 1973 October (Box 150, Folder 13)
    - Letters Sent, 1973 November (Box 150, Folder 14)
    - Letters Sent, 1973 December (Box 150, Folder 15)
    - Letters Sent, 1974 January (Box 150, Folder 16)
    - Letters Sent, 1974 February (Box 151, Folder 1)
    - Letters Sent, 1974 March (Box 151, Folder 2)
    - Letters Sent, 1974 April (Box 151, Folder 3)
    - Letters Sent, 1974 May (Box 151, Folder 4)
    - Letters Sent, 1974 June (Box 151, Folder 5)
    - Letters Sent, 1974 July (Box 151, Folder 6)
    - Letters Sent, 1974 September (Box 151, Folder 7)
    - Letters Sent, 1974 October (Box 151, Folder 8)
    - Letters Sent, 1974 November (Box 151, Folder 9)
    - Letters Sent, 1974 December (Box 151, Folder 10)
    - Letters Sent, 1975 January (Box 151, Folder 11)
    - Letters Sent, 1975 February (Box 151, Folder 12)
    - Letters Sent, 1975 March (Box 151, Folder 13)
    - Letters Sent, 1975 April (Box 151, Folder 14)
    - Letters Sent, 1975 May (Box 151, Folder 15)
    - Letters Sent, 1975 June (Box 151, Folder 16)
    - Letters Sent, 1975 September (Box 151, Folder 17)
    - Letters Sent, 1975 October (Box 151, Folder 18)
    - Letters Sent, 1975 November (Box 151, Folder 19)
    - Letters Sent, 1975 December (Box 151, Folder 20)
    - Letters Sent, 1976 January (Box 151, Folder 21)
    - Letters Sent, 1976 February (Box 152, Folder 1)
    - Letters Sent, 1976 March (Box 152, Folder 2)
    - Letters Sent, 1976 April (Box 152, Folder 3)
    - Letters Sent, 1976 May (Box 152, Folder 4)
    - Letters Sent, 1976 June (Box 152, Folder 5)
    - Letters Sent, 1976 September (Box 152, Folder 6)
    - Letters Sent, 1976 October (Box 152, Folder 7)
    - Letters Sent, 1976 November (Box 152, Folder 8)
    - Letters Sent, 1976 December (Box 152, Folder 9)
    - Letters Sent, 1977 January (Box 152, Folder 10)
    - Letters Sent, 1977 February (Box 152, Folder 11)
    - Letters Sent, 1977 March (Box 152, Folder 12)
    - Letters Sent, 1977 April (Box 152, Folder 13)
    - Letters Sent, 1977 May (Box 152, Folder 14)
    - Letters Sent, 1977 June (Box 152, Folder 15)
    - Letters Sent, 1977 September (Box 152, Folder 16)
    - Letters Sent, 1977 October (Box 152, Folder 17)
    - Letters Sent, 1977 November (Box 152, Folder 18)
    - Letters Sent, 1977 December (Box 152, Folder 19)
    - Letters Sent, 1978 (Box 152, Folder 20)
  - Inter-Office Correspondence, 1921-1953, 1.9:
    This subseries consists primarily of correspondence between the New York office and the Paris office and several additional folders of correspondence dating from 1940 to 1953 between Germain Seligman and sales associates César de Hauke, Rolf Hans Waegen, and Theresa D. Parker.
    The files are in chronological order, with each office having its own folder. Material within folders is generally in reverse chronological order. Mostly written in French, the correspondence concerns sales, clients, inventory, and general business concerns of the two offices. Curiously, 1928 has only one file, identified as correspondence with Paris. Dates may occasionally overlap folders.
    - Paris to New York, 1921 December-1922 May (Box 153, Folder 1)
    - New York to Paris, 1921 December-1922 April (Box 153, Folder 2)
    - Paris to New York, 1922 June-1922 September (Box 153, Folder 3)
    - New York to Paris, 1922 May-1922 September (Box 153, Folder 4)
    - Paris to New York, 1922 October-1922 December (Box 153, Folder 5)
    - New York to Paris, 1922 October-1922 December (Box 153, Folder 6)
    - Paris to New York, 1923 January (Box 153, Folder 7)
    - New York to Paris, 1923 January (Box 153, Folder 8)
    - Paris to New York, 1923 February (Box 153, Folder 9)
    - New York to Paris, 1923 February (Box 153, Folder 10)
    - Paris to New York, 1923 March (Box 153, Folder 11)
    - New York to Paris, 1923 March (Box 153, Folder 12)
    - Paris to New York, 1923 April (Box 153, Folder 13)
    - New York to Paris, 1923 April (Box 153, Folder 14)
    - Paris to New York, 1923 May (Box 153, Folder 15)
    - New York to Paris, 1923 May (Box 153, Folder 16)
    - Paris to New York, 1923 June (Box 153, Folder 17)
    - New York to Paris, 1923 June (Box 153, Folder 18)
    - Paris to New York, 1923 July (Box 153, Folder 19)
    - New York to Paris, 1923 July (Box 153, Folder 20)
    - Paris to New York, 1923 August (Box 153, Folder 21)
    - New York to Paris, 1923 August (Box 153, Folder 22)
    - Paris to New York, 1923 September (Box 154, Folder 1)
    - New York to Paris, 1923 September (Box 154, Folder 2)
    - Paris to New York, 1923 October (Box 154, Folder 3)
    - New York to Paris, 1923 October (Box 154, Folder 4)
    - Paris to New York, 1923 November (Box 154, Folder 5)
    - New York to Paris, 1923 November (Box 154, Folder 6)
    - Paris to New York, 1923 December (Box 154, Folder 7)
    - New York to Paris, 1923 December (Box 154, Folder 8)
    - Paris to New York, 1924 January (Box 154, Folder 9)
    - New York to Paris, 1924 January (Box 154, Folder 10)
    - Paris to New York, 1924 February (Box 154, Folder 11)
    - New York to Paris, 1924 February (Box 154, Folder 12)
    - Paris to New York, 1924 March (Box 154, Folder 13)
    - New York to Paris, 1924 March (Box 154, Folder 14)
    - Paris to New York, 1924 April (Box 154, Folder 15)
    - New York to Paris, 1924 April (Box 154, Folder 16)
    - Paris to New York, 1924 May (Box 154, Folder 17)
    - New York to Paris, 1924 May (Box 154, Folder 18)
    - Paris to New York, 1924 June (Box 154, Folder 19)
    - New York to Paris, 1924 June (Box 154, Folder 20)
    - Paris to New York, 1924 July (Box 154, Folder 21)
    - New York to Paris, 1924 July (Box 154, Folder 22)
    - Paris to New York, 1924 August (Box 154, Folder 23)
    - New York to Paris, 1924 August (Box 154, Folder 24)
    - Paris to New York, 1924 September (Box 154, Folder 25)
    - New York to Paris, 1924 September (Box 154, Folder 26)
    - Paris to New York, 1924 October (Box 154, Folder 27)
    - New York to Paris, 1924 October (Box 154, Folder 28)
    - Paris to New York, 1924 November (Box 154, Folder 29)
    - New York to Paris, 1924 November (Box 154, Folder 30)
    - Paris to New York, 1924 December (Box 154, Folder 31)
    - New York to Paris, 1924 December (Box 154, Folder 32)
    - Paris to New York, 1925 January (Box 155, Folder 1)
    - New York to Paris, 1925 January (Box 155, Folder 2)
    - Paris to New York, 1925 February (Box 155, Folder 3)
    - New York to Paris, 1925 February (Box 155, Folder 4)
    - Paris to New York, 1925 March (Box 155, Folder 5)
    - New York to Paris, 1925 March (Box 155, Folder 6)
    - Paris to New York, 1925 April (Box 155, Folder 7)
    - New York to Paris, 1925 April (Box 155, Folder 8)
    - Paris to New York, 1925 May (Box 155, Folder 9)
    - New York to Paris, 1925 May (Box 155, Folder 10)
    - Paris to New York, 1925 June (Box 155, Folder 11)
    - New York to Paris, 1925 June (Box 155, Folder 12)
    - Paris to New York, 1925 July (Box 155, Folder 13)
    - New York to Paris, 1925 July (Box 155, Folder 14)
    - Paris to New York, 1925 August (Box 155, Folder 15)
    - New York to Paris, 1925 August (Box 155, Folder 16)
    - Paris to New York, 1925 September (Box 155, Folder 17)
    - New York to Paris, 1925 September (Box 155, Folder 18)
    - Paris to New York, 1925 October (Box 155, Folder 19)
    - New York to Paris, 1925 October (Box 155, Folder 20)
    - Paris to New York, 1925 November (Box 155, Folder 21)
    - New York to Paris, 1925 November (Box 155, Folder 22)
    - Paris to New York, 1925 December (Box 155, Folder 23)
    - New York to Paris, 1925 December (Box 155, Folder 24)
    - Paris to New York, 1926 January (Box 156, Folder 1)
    - New York to Paris, 1926 January (Box 156, Folder 2)
    - Paris to New York, 1926 February (Box 156, Folder 3)
    - New York to Paris, 1926 February (Box 156, Folder 4)
    - Paris to New York, 1926 March (Box 156, Folder 5)
    - New York to Paris, 1926 March (Box 156, Folder 6)
    - Paris to New York, 1926 April (Box 156, Folder 7)
    - New York to Paris, 1926 April (Box 156, Folder 8)
    - Paris to New York, 1926 May (Box 156, Folder 9)
    - New York to Paris, 1926 May (Box 156, Folder 10)
    - Paris to New York, 1926 June (Box 156, Folder 11)
    - New York to Paris, 1926 June (Box 156, Folder 12)
    - Paris to New York, 1926 July (Box 156, Folder 13)
    - New York to Paris, 1926 July (Box 156, Folder 14)
    - Paris to New York, 1926 August (Box 156, Folder 15)
    - New York to Paris, 1926 August (Box 156, Folder 16)
    - Paris to New York, 1926 September (Box 156, Folder 17)
    - New York to Paris, 1926 September (Box 156, Folder 18)
    - Paris to New York, 1926 October (Box 156, Folder 19)
    - New York to Paris, 1926 October (Box 156, Folder 20)
    - Paris to New York, 1926 November (Box 156, Folder 21)
    - New York to Paris, 1926 November (Box 156, Folder 22)
    - Paris to New York, 1926 December (Box 156, Folder 23)
    - New York to Paris, 1926 December (Box 156, Folder 24)
    - Paris to New York, 1927 January (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - New York to Paris, 1927 January (Box 157, Folder 2)
    - Paris to New York, 1927 February (Box 157, Folder 3)
    - New York to Paris, 1927 February (Box 157, Folder 4)
    - Paris to New York, 1927 March (Box 157, Folder 5)
    - New York to Paris, 1927 March (Box 157, Folder 6)
    - Paris to New York, 1927 April (Box 157, Folder 7)
    - New York to Paris, 1927 April (Box 157, Folder 8)
    - Paris to New York, 1927 May (Box 157, Folder 9)
    - New York to Paris, 1927 May (Box 157, Folder 10)
    - Paris to New York, 1927 June (Box 157, Folder 11)
    - New York to Paris, 1927 June (Box 157, Folder 12)
    - Paris to New York, 1927 July (Box 157, Folder 13)
    - New York to Paris, 1927 July (Box 157, Folder 14)
    - Paris to New York, 1927 August (Box 157, Folder 15)
    - New York to Paris, 1927 August (Box 157, Folder 16)
    - Paris to New York, 1927 September (Box 157, Folder 17)
    - 1927 September New York to Paris (Box 157, Folder 18)
    - 1927 October Paris to New York (Box 157, Folder 19)
    - 1927 October New York to Paris (Box 157, Folder 20)
    - 1927 November Paris to New York (Box 157, Folder 21)
    - 1927 November New York to Paris (Box 157, Folder 22)
    - 1927 December Paris to New York (Box 157, Folder 23)
    - 1927 December New York to Paris (Box 157, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence with Paris, 1928 (Box 158, Folder 1)
      (only one file for 1928)
    - 1929 January Paris to New York (Box 158, Folder 2)
    - 1929 January New York to Paris (Box 158, Folder 3)
    - 1929 February Paris to New York (Box 158, Folder 4)
    - 1929 February New York to Paris (Box 158, Folder 5)
    - 1929 March Paris to New York (Box 158, Folder 6)
    - 1929 March New York to Paris (Box 158, Folder 7)
    - 1929 April Paris to New York (Box 158, Folder 8)
    - 1929 April New York to Paris (Box 158, Folder 9)
    - 1929 May Paris to New York (Box 158, Folder 10)
    - 1929 May New York to Paris (Box 158, Folder 11)
    - 1929 June Paris to New York (Box 158, Folder 12)
    - 1929 June New York to Paris (Box 158, Folder 13)
    - 1929 July Paris to New York (Box 158, Folder 14)
    - 1929 July New York to Paris (Box 158, Folder 15)
    - 1929 August Paris to New York (Box 158, Folder 16)
    - 1929 August New York to Paris (Box 158, Folder 17)
    - 1929 September Paris to New York (Box 158, Folder 18)
    - 1929 September New York to Paris (Box 158, Folder 19)
    - 1929 October Paris to New York (Box 158, Folder 20)
    - 1929 October New York to Paris (Box 158, Folder 21)
    - 1929 November Paris to New York (Box 158, Folder 22)
    - 1929 November New York to Paris (Box 158, Folder 23)
    - 1929 December Paris to New York (Box 158, Folder 24)
    - 1929 December New York to Paris (Box 158, Folder 25)
    - 1930 January Paris to New York (Box 158, Folder 26)
    - 1930 January New York to Paris (Box 158, Folder 27)
    - 1930 February Paris to New York (Box 158, Folder 28)
    - 1930 February New York to Paris (Box 158, Folder 29)
    - 1930 March Paris to New York (Box 158, Folder 30)
    - 1930 March New York to Paris (Box 158, Folder 31)
    - 1930 April Paris to New York (Box 159, Folder 1)
    - 1930 April New York to Paris (Box 159, Folder 2)
    - 1930 May Paris to New York (Box 159, Folder 3)
    - 1930 May New York to Paris (Box 159, Folder 4)
    - 1930 June Paris to New York (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - 1930 June New York to Paris (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - 1930 July Paris to New York (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - 1930 July New York to Paris (Box 159, Folder 8)
    - 1930 August Paris to New York (Box 159, Folder 9)
    - 1930 August New York to Paris (Box 159, Folder 10)
    - 1930 September Paris to New York (Box 159, Folder 11)
    - 1930 September New York to Paris (Box 159, Folder 12)
    - 1930 October Paris to New York (Box 159, Folder 13)
    - 1930 October New York to Paris (Box 159, Folder 14)
    - 1930 November Paris to New York (Box 159, Folder 15)
    - 1930 November New York to Paris (Box 159, Folder 16)
    - 1930 December Paris to New York (Box 159, Folder 17)
    - 1930 December New York to Paris (Box 159, Folder 18)
    - 1931 January Paris to New York (Box 159, Folder 19)
    - 1931 January New York to Paris (Box 159, Folder 20)
    - 1931 February Paris to New York (Box 159, Folder 21)
    - 1931 February New York to Paris (Box 159, Folder 22)
    - 1931 March Paris to New York (Box 159, Folder 23)
    - 1931 March New York to Paris (Box 159, Folder 24)
    - 1931 April Paris to New York (Box 159, Folder 25)
    - 1931 April New York to Paris (Box 159, Folder 26)
    - 1931 May Paris to New York (Box 159, Folder 27)
    - 1931 May New York to Paris (Box 159, Folder 28)
    - 1931 June Paris to New York (Box 159, Folder 29)
    - 1931 June New York to Paris (Box 159, Folder 30)
    - 1931 July Paris to New York (Box 159, Folder 31)
    - 1931 July New York to Paris (Box 159, Folder 32)
    - 1931 August Paris to New York (Box 160, Folder 1)
    - 1931 August New York to Paris (Box 160, Folder 2)
    - 1931 September Paris to New York (Box 160, Folder 3)
    - 1931 September New York to Paris (Box 160, Folder 4)
    - 1931 October Paris to New York (Box 160, Folder 5)
    - 1931 October New York to Paris (Box 160, Folder 6)
    - 1931 November Paris to New York (Box 160, Folder 7)
    - 1931 November New York to Paris (Box 160, Folder 8)
    - 1931 December Paris to New York (Box 160, Folder 9)
    - 1931 December New York to Paris (Box 160, Folder 10)
    - 1932 January Paris to New York (Box 160, Folder 11)
    - 1932 January New York to Paris (Box 160, Folder 12)
    - 1932 February Paris to New York (Box 160, Folder 13)
    - 1932 February New York to Paris (Box 160, Folder 14)
    - 1932 March Paris to New York (Box 160, Folder 15)
    - 1932 March New York to Paris (Box 160, Folder 16)
    - 1932 April Paris to New York (Box 160, Folder 17)
    - 1932 April New York to Paris (Box 160, Folder 18)
    - 1932 May Paris to New York (Box 160, Folder 19)
    - 1932 May New York to Paris (Box 160, Folder 20)
    - 1932 June Paris to New York (Box 160, Folder 21)
    - 1932 June New York to Paris (Box 160, Folder 22)
    - 1932 July Paris to New York (Box 160, Folder 23)
    - 1932 July New York to Paris (Box 160, Folder 24)
    - 1932 August Paris to New York (Box 160, Folder 25)
    - 1932 August New York to Paris (Box 160, Folder 26)
    - 1932 September Paris to New York (Box 160, Folder 27)
    - 1932 September New York to Paris (Box 160, Folder 28)
    - 1932 October Paris to New York (Box 160, Folder 29)
    - 1932 October New York to Paris (Box 160, Folder 30)
    - 1932 November Paris to New York (Box 160, Folder 31)
    - 1932 November New York to Paris (Box 160, Folder 32)